A Guide to the Records of the University Photographer, 1965-1985
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Records of the University Photographer 1965-1985
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-5/7/2.021
The collection consists of photographic contact sheets of University photographer Dave Skinner.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the university library on 2002 November 7.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of the Records of the University Photographer.
Arrangement
Arranged by subject.
Contents List
- ACC Tournament 1975-1976 (Box 1)
- Admissions 1982 (Box 1)
- Aerial Photos 1972 (Box 1)
- Afro-American Affairs 1975-1987 (Box 1)
- Alderman Library 1972-1984 (Box 1)
- Alumni Activities 1973-1977 (Box 1)
- Alumni Summer on the Lawn 1981 (Box 1)
- Art Department n.d. (Box 1)
- Architecture School 1971-1972 (Box 1)
- Astronomy Department 1973-1975 (Box 1)
- Athletics, Baseball 1979-1982 (Box 1)
- Athletics, Men's Basketball (3 folders) 1979-1982 (Box 1)
- Athletics, Women's Basketball 1978-1982 (Box 1)
- Athletics, Field Hockey 1979-1982 (Box 1)
- Athletics, Football I (4 folders) 1973-1982 (Box 1)
- Athletics, Football II (3 folders) 1977-1983 (Box 2)
- Athletics, Intramurals (5 folders) 1975-1982 (Box 2)
- Athletics, Lacrosse (2 folders) 1975-1982 (Box 2)
- Athletics, Miscellaneous (3 folders) 1972-1982 (Box 2)
- Athletics, Rugby, Women's 1979 (Box 2)
- Athletics, Soccer 1978-1982 (Box 2)
- Athletics, Tennis 1978-1982 (Box 2)
- Athletics, Track (2 folders) 1976-1982 (Box 2)
- Athletics, Women (3 folders) 1974-1987 (Box 2)
- Back to School (4 folders) 1975-1985 (Box 3)
- Barrett Room and Clifton Waller Barrett 1971 (Box 3)
- Bayly Museum 1976-1983 (Box 3)
- Beta Bridge 1981 (Box 3)
- Biology Department 1971-1979 (Box 3)
- Black Student Activities 1974-1981 (Box 3)
- Blandy Farm 1973-1974 (Box 3)
- Board of Visitors 1976-1979 (Box 3)
- Buildings 1974-1984 (Box 3)
- Buckingham Center 1971 (Box 3)
- Cabell Hall n.d. (Box 3)
- Career Opportunities Institute 1980 (Box 3)
- Career Planning and Placement 1983 (Box 3)
- Carruthers Hall 1981 (Box 3)
- Jimmy Carter Visit 1987 (Box 3)
- Chemistry Department 1977 (Box 3)
- Classes 1974-1995 (Box 3)
- Clemons Library 1980-1982 (Box 3)
- College of Arts and Sciences 1981-1983 (Box 3)
- Colonnade 1980-1982 (Box 3)
- Commonwealth Day (4 folders) 1974-1984 (Box 3)
- Computing Center 1976 (Box 3)
- Commerce School (3 folders) 1978-1982 (Box 3)
- Concerts 1978 (Box 4)
- Virginius Dabney 1981 (Box 4)
- Dalai Lama's Visit 1979 (Box 4)
- Darden School (3 folders) 1975-1982 (Box 4)
- Dedication of Clemons Library 1982 (Box 4)
- Demonstrations 1979 (Box 4)
- Dormitories 1975-1978 (Box 4)
- Drama: Building, Virginia Players, Heritage Theater 1973-1978 (Box 4)
- Easters (3 folders) 1976-1984 (Box 4)
- Education School 1976-1982 (Box 4)
- Federal Executive Institute 1969 (Box 4)
- Finals and Class Valediction (5 folders) 1980-1985 (Box 4)
- Finals (5 folders) 1971-1982 (Box 4)
- Engineering and Applied Sciences 1974-1981 (Box 5)
- Environmental Sciences 1976-1982 (Box 5)
- Fall Convocation 1974-1983 (Box 5)
- William Faulkner Exhibit Opening 1975 (Box 5)
- Fires 1978-1979 (Box 5)
- Food Service 1975-1982 (Box 5)
- Founder's Day (3 folders) 1973-1983 (Box 5)
- Fraternities 1980-1984 (Box 5)
- Fraternities and Sororities 1977-1980 (Box 5)
- French Department 1980 (Box 5)
- Gardens-East 1965-1968 (Box 5)
- Garrett Hall 1981 (Box 5)
- General Assembly 1981 (Box 5)
- Glass Hat 1975 (Box 5)
- Governors 1977 (Box 5)
- Grounds-Architecture 1977-1982 (Box 5)
- Grounds-Informal 1968-1982 (Box 5)
- Honor Committee 1976 (Box 5)
- Wednesday Group, House of Representatives 1980 (Box 5)
- Housing 1978-1979 (Box 5)
- Luther P. Jackson House 1977 (Box 5)
- JAG School 1979 (Box 5)
- Jeffersonian Legacies 1992 (Box 5)
- Jefferson Scholars 1983 (Box 5)
- Jordan Hall 1977 (Box 5)
- Institute of Government 1981 (Box 5)
- Law School (2 folders) 1975-1984 (Box 5)
- The Lawn 1977-1978 (Box 5)
- Libraries n.d. (Box 5)
- McCormick Observatory 1977 (Box 5)
- McLeod Hall 1972 (Box 5)
- Madison Bowl 1977 (Box 5)
- Materials Science 1977 (Box 5)
- Mechanical Engineering 1970-1975 (Box 5)
- Medical Center, Blue Ridge 1981 (Box 5)
- Medical Center, Children's Rehabilitation 1984 (Box 5)
- Medical Center, General 1982-1985 (Box 5)
- Medical Center, Hospital 1973-1984 (Box 5)
- Medical Center, Medical School 1971-1983 (Box 5)
- Medical Center, Nursing School 1971-1981 (Box 5)
- Mellott (2 folders) n.d. (Box 6)
- Miller Center 1978-1982 (Box 6)
- Miscellaneous 1968-1978 (Box 6)
- Monroe Hall 1982 (Box 6)
- Mountain Lake Biological Station 1972 (Box 6)
- Music Department (3 folders) 1976-1982 (Box 6)
- North Grounds 1979 (Box 6)
- Nuclear Reactor n.d. (Box 6)
- Nursing 1971 (Box 6)
- Observatory Dining Building 1975 (Box 6)
- Parent's Day 1976-1985 (Box 6)
- Parking and Transportation 1977 (Box 6)
- Pavilions 1975-1986 (Box 6)
- Pavilion XI 1975 (Box 6)
- Pavilions, Out of Date n.d. (Box 6)
- Peabody Hall 1982 (Box 6)
- PEN/Faulkner Award 1981 (Box 6)
- Personnel 1981 (Box 6)
- Physical Plant 1982-1983 (Box 6)
- Physics 1975-1981 (Box 6)
- Edgar Allan Poe Weekend and Poe Room 1979 (Box 6)
- Edgar Allan Poe Weekend 1981 (Box 6)
- Poetry Festival 1973-1980 (Box 6)
- Pop Concerts 1979 (Box 6)
- Portraits (informal) n.d. (Box 6)
- President's Office 1979 (Box 6)
- Press Conference 1982 (Box 6)
- Professors Emeriti 1974 (Box 6)
- Psychology Department 1977 (Box 6)
- Queens Visit 1976 (Box 6)
- Range-West 1980 (Box 6)
- Retirees 1984 (Box 6)
- Retiring Professors 1981 (Box 6)
- ROTC 1976-1982 (Box 6)
- Rotunda 1976-1981 (Box 6)
- Rotunda Restoration 1973-1976 (Box 6)
- Scott Stadium n.d. (Box 6)
- Service Awards 1980-1982 (Box 6)
- Speakers (2 folders) 1975-1981 (Box 6)
- Sponsors Hall 1978-1980 (Box 6)
- Student Affairs 1981 (Box 7)
- Student Activities 1979-1984 (Box 7)
- Student Life, Social n.d. (Box 7)
- Student Life (4 folders) 1974-1983 (Box 7)
- Telephone System 1982 (Box 7)
- United Way 1978-1982 (Box 7)
- Weather Shots 1974-1980 (Box 7)
- Virginia Academy of Sciences 1980 (Box 7)
- Carter G. Woodson Institute 1982 (Box 7)